Jose G. Aquino III

Aspiring Web Developer and Programmer

SUMMARY

Currently a 4th year student in De La Salle University - Manila taking up BS Information Systems. Playing around with computers has been my interest ever since I was young. Majority of my experiences involve development of web applications using javascript and mysql. I have also tried playing around with selenium for automating unit tests on my school projects and creating script files as shortcuts for my personal computer.

EXPERIENCE

FUELCiti POS - Full Stack Developer 🖸

(March 2022 - Present)

FUELCiti is a self-owned gasoline station opened by my parents. I created a POS that assists the cashier in recording transactions and generating daily reports about their sales. The system uses java as its programming language and MySQL as its database.

LA Rice Mill CMS - Programmer

(February 2021 - Present)

As part of our thesis requirement, we created a Crop Management System for LA Rice Mill, a milling service based in Mindoro. Our group of four created a web application that provides management of multiple farms through the use of Satellite technology. The system uses NodeJs framework and MySQL as its database.

JMA C-Stem - Programmer

(June 2020 - January 2021)

JMA C-stem is a Supply Chain Management System developed by my thesis group for JM Aquino Trading & Services, a cement dealer based in Batangas City. The system supports the business by keeping track of purchases, sales and logistics. The system uses NodeJs framework and MySQL as its database.

CONTACT

+63 917 302 8128

Q Gulod Itaas, Batangas City, Philippines

joseiiiaquino@gmail.com

https://github.com/y2saur

in linkedin.com/in/jose-iii-aquino

EDUCATION

De La Salle University, Manila BS-Information Systems 2018 - Present

De La Salle University, Manila Senior High School 2016 - 2018

De La Salle Lipa Junior High School 2012 - 2016

Stonyhurst Southville International School, Batangas Campus Elementary School 2004 - 2012

SKILLS

Languages: C, Java, Javascripts,

Html, CSS, Python **Frameworks:** NodeJs

Tools: JQuery, Git, Selenium **Databases:** SQL (MySQL, SQLite), MongoDB, Firebase